goober.com 2007-10-11

# Privacy Policy for the Protection of Your Privacy

The protection of your privacy is our highest priority. Therefor, goober sets a high value on the protection and security of your data and feels obliged to handle your individual-related data as well as your communication data as confidential as possible.  
Below, we inform you about how your individual-related data is generated in goober and with which accuracy and diligence we deal with it.  
Furthermore, you will find out how you can share these data with other users.

These privacy terms will complement the general terms and conditions as well as the license agreement for the utilization of goober.

**1\. Information of several terms**

"Individual-related data" are all particulars of your personal or businesslike circumstances.

"Registration data" is the individual-related data that has to be stated at registration for the goober services.

"Goober platforms" describes the websites and the access software on which goober provides services.

"Goober members" are the users who are registered on the goober platforms.

"Goober services" includes the services provided on the goober platforms for which the user has to register.

"Forums" include the forums, groups and related services provided by goober services.

**2\. Policies to process individual-related data**

Goober sets the following policies to protect your individual-related data:

The ascertainment, processing and utilization of individual-related data takes place in accordance with the German Data Protection Act and the privacy terms of the European Union.

Goober utilizes your individual-related data exclusively to enable you to use the internet services provided by goober for which you have to register. In no case will goober sell your individual-related data or show it to a third person for any reason, for instance for promotional or marketing purposes. 

Despite of some information, like username and goober ID, you decide yourself which of the individual-related data can be viewed by other goober members.Your individual-related data, or parts of it, is only visible to non-members of goober when you explicitly allowed it.

**3\. Right of access to personal data**

You can always get access to your data you saved in goober, its origin and function. Furthermore, you have the right to correct, delete and lock wrong data. Please send an e-mail with your questions to support@goobernetworks.com.

**4\. Registration information**

As necessary requirement for the efficiency of goober services, goober has to get and process registration information from certain individual-related data at your registration. This data is the following:

\- Username   
\- Password 

Within goober services, you will be addressed, identified and associated by your username. Other goober users are in no way and at no time able to see your password. Goober will never forward your data to a third person.   
There may be other optional individual-related data at registration:

\- First name  
\- Last name  
\- E-mail address

The indication of first and last name as well as e-mail address are optional. This supplement, however, can be very helpful for other goober members to associate the username with a certain person. The e-mail address should help communication between goober and members and respectively when a member forgot his/her username or password. Goober will in no case forward the e-mail address to any third person or let any other person take notice of it. 

**5\. Additional optional information**

Goober provides the option to add voluntary information to support goober members to find other people with similar interests and, thus, get in contact with the right person. These include your private interests, your business, your private or business contacts, your picture etc.  
You choose yourself which goober members are allowed to see this additional information and which are not. Only goober members whom you allowed to see this additional optional information by giving them special rights can view it.   
If you wish to join special goober services, like the network goober Friends, it is however necessary that your personal profile can be seen by everyone.

User information

\- Own picture

Public profile information

\- Last name  
\- First name  
\- Gender  
\- Age (calculated)  
\- Country  
\- Federal state  
\- Contact language  
\- Interests  
\- About me / My slogan

Business information

\- Status   
\- Company   
\- Sector   
\- Job   
\- Training   
\- Professional interests  
\- Professional offer  
\- Website

**6\. Forums**

Every forum provided by goober has one or several moderators. The respective moderator decides whether a forum is public or only accessible by a certain group of people. It is also the moderator's decision who has the permission to read and write in this specific forum. This information will be shown for the respective forum and will be visible to goober members and depending on the enabling of the moderator where appropriate also for non-members.   
When a forum of the goober services is labeled as "public" and the moderator did not restrict the access rights of the respective forum, the entries in the forum can not only be viewed by goober members but also by non-members.

**7\. Invitations**

Goober members have the opportunity to invite other people to join goober. The information which will be send with the invitation by goober is:

\- Your username  
\- Your user ID  
\- Optional information with a description field in which you can write your own message

**8\. Cookies**

After your registration, goober services uses cookies to be able to identify you during your session. They are also used to improve usability, efficiency and security. Cookies are text files which are filed on your computer and saved by your browser. After your session is ended, the cookie expires automatically.They are automatically deleted after your visit. You can save this cookie permanently for an automatic login with the function "automatically sign in at program start". The cookie now contains parts of your login details in encrypted format. 

**9\. Log files**

A protocol file is created with every page view in which access data, the server log, is stored. In this process, your IP address (identification of your computer is possible), the product information of the used browser, the remote host (name and IP address of the computer which requests the site), time, status, the amount of data transferred, as well as the name of the site from which you came to the requested site (referrer) will be recorded. For this purpose, goober applies the standard combined log file format from the apache web server and uses the protocol data anonymized, this means without reference or any other hints that would lead to your person. This data will only be used for statistical evaluation (e.g. to evaluate the times of the day with the most requests) and to analyse errors (e.g. inaccurate links).

If there is any suspicion that somebody is using goober platforms in an illegal or antinomian way or contrary to contract, goober reserves the right to check the log files for the last known IP address of these goober members later. 

**10\. Search functions**   
The goober services give you the possibility to use different search functions at divers places. You get support to find other goober members with similar interests or to get in contact with other goober members who offer exactly that what you were looking for.

**11\. Minimum age**   
The minimum age for a membership with goober is 18 years.

**12\. Changes of the privacy policy**

Goober reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. There is no reason for a contractual or any other formal right towards one party. Goober will inform you of any changes regarding this privacy policy. You will receive this information via e-mail which you will be asked for during the registration process.

Version: 16.12.2005
